export default  [
  {
    "category": "Chris",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "Which answer does not correctly describe the new, larger GitHub-hosted runners?",
    "correct_answer": "Java installed by default",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Available for Linux and Windows",
        "Static IP ranges available",
        "Auto-scaled runners by GitHub"
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Chris",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "How would you define a set of recommended extensions for a Codespace?",
    "correct_answer": "Configure them in the extensions property of devcontainer.json",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Install them in the dockerfile",
        "Setup a script to install in the dotfiles",
        "Use settings sync to install the specific extensions"
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Chris",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "Which answer does not correctly describe code scanning in GitHub Advanced Security?",
    "correct_answer": "Third-party tools that output into a CSV format can be integrated with Code Scanning",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Third-party analysis tools can be run, and results imported to GitHub Code Scanning",
      "CodeQL treats code like data, so you can write queries to find patterns in code.",
      "Java is supported by GitHub's code analysis engine, CodeQL"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Chris",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "Which Github tool can detect vulnerabilities in the dependencies of your Github repository?",
    "correct_answer": "Dependabot",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Github copilot",
        "Github scanning",
        "Vulneracheck",
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Chris",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "What is Github Artifacts?",
    "correct_answer": "A way to store data produced by a workflow",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "A cloud storage solution from Github",
        "A place to store source code",
        "A solution for an open issue",
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Chris",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "What is Github Actions?",
    "correct_answer": "A platform that allows you to automate CI/CD (Build, Test, Deployment), and react to other GitHub events.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "A bot that helps you improve your DevOps Automation",
        "A tool that helps you take action on security issues inside your codebase.",
        "An AI pair programmer",
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Chris",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "What tool can help you create a quick and consistent development environment?",
    "correct_answer": "GitHub Codespaces",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "GitHub Copilot",
        "GitHub Actions",
        "GitHub Container Registry",
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "PowerBI",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "GitHub secret scanning is available",
    "correct_answer": "on private repos with GitHub Advanced Security and public repos on github.com",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Only private repos on github.com",
        "GitHub Enterprise Server",
        "Only public repos on github.com"
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Julien",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "In JavaScript, what is the result of \"0.1+0.2\"?",
    "correct_answer": "0.30000000000000004",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "0.3",
        "0",
        "NaN"
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "PowerBI",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "What is Azure Spring Apps?",
    "correct_answer": "Managed service for hosting Spring Apps",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "A service to deploy only a single Spring Boot app",
        "A new Spring framework",
        "A new IaaS solution for hosting Spring Apps"
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "PowerBI",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "Which one(s) of these Azure solutions can you use to deploy Spring Cloud Apps?",
    "correct_answer": "Azure Spring Apps",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Azure Spring Cloud",
        "Azure Spring Framework",
        "All the answers"
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "PowerBI",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "Which one(s) of these Azure solutions can you use to deploy containers?",
    "correct_answer": "All the answers",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Azure Container Instances",
        "Azure Kubernetes Service",
        "Azure Container Apps"
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "PowerBI",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "Which Azure Messaging solution supports JMS?",
    "correct_answer": "Azure Service Bus",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Azure Event Grid",
        "Azure Event Hub",
        "Azure Queue Storage"
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "PowerBI",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "Which GitHub Action configures Java on a GitHub runner?",
    "correct_answer": "actions/setup-java",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "actions/initialise-java",
        "actions/configure-java",
        "actions/java-setup"
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "PowerBI",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "What is Github Artifacts?",
    "correct_answer": "A way to store data produced by a workflow",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "A cloud storage solution from Github",
        "A place to store source code",
        "A change request to your code base"
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "PowerBI",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "Which Microsoft product helps developers starting a new project quickly and efficiently?",
    "correct_answer": "Azure Dev Box",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Azure Virtual Desktop",
        "Windows 365",
        "Visual Workshop"
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "PowerBI",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "Which editor integrates with Azure",
    "correct_answer": "IntelliJ",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "vim",
        "nano",
        "notepad++"
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "PowerBI",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "What is an octopus merge?",
    "correct_answer": "It takes two or more branches and merge them in a single branch",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "It stages several commits and merges them at once",
        "It's a type of octopus living in the atlantic ocean",
        "It's a merge done with Git Kraken"
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "PowerBI",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "What is a protected branch in Github?",
    "correct_answer": "A branch which you must meet certain standards to be able to commit to it",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "A secured branch which only accepts perfect code",
        "A hidden branch, and only available for specific users or groups",
        "A branch used to work on security features"
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "PowerBI",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "Why would you create a pull request?",
    "correct_answer": "To ask colleagues/community for code review before merging",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "To pull code from a repository",
        "To ask colleagues/community for help",
        "To contact Microsoft support"
      ]
  },
  {
    "category": "PowerBI",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "How many Azure components do you need to create an approval flow using Java?",
    "correct_answer": "1",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "2",
        "3",
        "4"
      ]
  }
]